http://www.novathin.com/privacy-policy.html

Our ProductsOur Products Our Absorbent Cores ApplicationsAbout EAMAbout EAM Industry Resources Careers Domtar EverydayContact UsRequest SamplesEAM Corporation 912-588-2600 2075 Sunset Blvd.Jesup, GA, USA 31545Privacy PolicyHave a question? Contact us herePrivacy PolicyEAM Corporation ("EAM") is committed to and recognizes your need for protection and privacy issues on the Internet. In general, you can visit eamcorporation.com ("Website") without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. We may collect the IP addresses and / or domain names of visitors for site administration purposes, such as to analyze this data for trends and statistics. No personal information is obtained, but the patterns of usage may be tracked and monitored.Collecting personal identifiable informationThere are times when we may collect personal information from you; for example, when you are sending an information request. We may collect the following information from you voluntarily:NameCompanyEmail addressPhone numberRemoving or updating personal informationIf you change your mind or wish to update personal information, we will endeavor to correct, update or remove the personal data you give us. You may at any time revise your personal information or question it by directly contacting us at info@eamcorp.com. EAM reserves the right to disclose user information in special cases, when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other Web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose personal information in response to a subpoena, when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or to respond to an emergency situation.
